sup everyone timbers worthy feel fast
here with a very special beauty now I'm
back again with another kick-ass Sonic
Underground recipe you may remember my
in shock and I'm chilly like I
speak well since you all love that I
thought hey you know what I'll
show them another one and so so this
today is going to be my special bow
Bardonic ramen I mean you're maybe
wondering what makes about Bardonic well
you'll find now I'll give you a hint
yellow for Barbie blue like
Sonic's ass now of course for the
ingredients we have stovetop ramen I
prefer to use chicken because it's like
when you have a seasoning it's you're
like Barbie and but but beef will
work that's fine we've got a banana and
and the next we got blue raspberry soda
what you can what will your C
now we'll show first off we're going to
add our soda to the pan which which we
will be using in a minute there we go
next we want add the next part is your
choice but I love adding the B seasoning
that comes with it because adds a bit of
Tang eNOS like it's like a little pop in
your mouth it's like Batman punching you
in the face
I forgot it I forgot you turn that
on this is now we will let that cook for
a few minutes of just boiling it
while this is happening we won't cut the
banana banana you're not gonna need you
caught that much because you're gonna
smush it in into the ramen later
let me fit that beast over so that's a
beef can get in those juices and
I almost forgot you're going to need to
add about a tablespoon of butter and
the reason that is because see I
found what is this the soda pop
it's so when it gets hot it can become
very sticky so you need some birth to
kind of dilute it and to all five
again as you can see it's kind of the
ramen is slowly turning blue locks on it
when it's done when it when he brews
nice and showing you like Bobby's
flowing golden manly locks and
then it'll be good speed sorry Condor
Sonic on the ground they made of a the
mama will be found
Sonic on the ground as you can see the
ramen is hard to break up and
that's exactly what we want now about
this time is what you want to like it
add in the banana and
and you're going to want to cut that up
and cut that up and next to mush it
around
oh that's me that smells good oh I love
that I love this
you love it too you can't even
smell it if you want to know what smell
like what the smells I can think of
think of spaghetti with like banana and
sugar if that doesn't sound good to you
well you're just wrong many people might
say that this combination of food is
weird and I can get that but I'm not
that you got you got some vision I'm not
normal I'm weird I'm crazy you wanna be
like me cuz know what no one's buying
Mitch this looks like it's about ready
to server up and enjoy just go stir this
up oh I gotta get like a fork - must be
pronounced motion here we go
come on listen to me yeah that's good
hold on let me just get like a little
pieces taster
as you can see you probably can't tell
but the ramen I'll be drawing a bit of
the blue colour from the soda pop from
that's good now serve this up oh
oh yes oh look at that you wanna close
up I know you do look at that
this lot just like it yello-ha me get my
chopsticks for this Oh daddy
mmm
as you could see there is like a yellow
like a little sweet chicken nugget
that's Bobby if I shove up Sonic's ass
let me just have a bother good oh that's
hot
oh that's the I'm in the banana
with ramen Oh like - yo things in a soup
of blue soda furball for Sonic can you
get better than this
I don't think so oh my God I need
another bad this is too much
I'm I need a bigger bass board I need a
fork you shovel this in my mouth
oh yes oh damn I spilled some look at
that look how much I just fell I
don't just go on my mouth anyway mmm
love that mmm you can make this -
all I showed you it's like what
a doll to make all this that's the good
that's the good
Golden Corral this is it